[Music]
Come on come on come on go, it's a good hour
Hey
Shanti come on go, it's a good hour [
Music]
[Music] All is empty, you put it on the empty basket, all is good, bring water in the soil, hey water, I whistle on saying, an hour and a half hour, let's read it [Music] [Music]
Hey note on the table, newspaper, hey
listen, newspaper,
hey
note [Music]
look at the newspaper,
slowly listen, it's
not okay, kick it, kick it,
come quickly, Delhi, hey kick it,
one school,
give me half the school,
school is closed
[Music]
Hey note, I'm going to school today too, like school [Music] Hey note, stay, stay, hey note, I'm going to school [
Music]
[Music]
[Screaming voice]
Stay in the street, that school is left, then
you see the school,
first
you
notice, you see the
bicycle, then you
see the girl,
and then
you are very supiya
[Music]
Puda Puda
ko,
hey  Let's
go to school, there is a class,
who is Punia ji?
[Music]
Oh,
so
fine, see all the questions, answers,
sir, who are
you, sir?
1948,
August 15th
[Laughter] Oh, this [ __ ],
father's
[
Music] in this, the whole class, you are father's sand, father's teeth,
who is the father, I am the father, Baba, the badass, father
[Laughter] God, Mahatma Gandhi, Lal Gandhi, Mahatma Gandhi, sorry, sorry, all, Mahatma Gandhi's wife's name, Mahatma Gandhi's Murr, who is the publicity sir, Jawaharlal Nehru, oh, who is the first Prime Minister, all give the
wrong answer, you
fools ...
Down the way, if you go and find
happiness,
brother, you are
spoiling the whole thing
[Music]
[Music] What have you done to the
happiness of the actress, then Suna Ja, give me a
surprise
[Music]
Oh, who is the postman, Suna, who is the
postman, then who is
Sunil, who is Koni, then Suna Ja, Suna Ja,
who is Suni, who is Suni, who is Jakhila,
take the doctor,
Babu,
water,
medicine, medical,
medical, anyone
[Music]
we